adoptim.com 2015-12-18

# AdOptim - Privacy

Adoptim allows users (herein referred to as advertisers) to purchase mobile advertisements from leading ad-exchanges and also allows mobile application publishers (herein referred to as publishers) to provide ad space for advertisers to place their ads. This Privacy Policy describes: (a) how Adoptim. (“we” or “us” or “our”) collects information from advertisers and publishers (b) how we consequently use that information to create a rich product experience; and (c) how we share that information with our publishers, advertiser and other third parties.

### A/ About this policy

This Privacy Policy governs our use and disclosure of information that we collect when you visit a website that directly or indirectly uses the [Posu.me](http://posu.me/) services, or view advertisements we serve. This Privacy Policy does not otherwise apply to the practices of other websites, such as those of our publishers and advertiser, or other services or companies that we do not own, manage or control. We do not control the privacy practices of such third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties when you use their services.

### B/ Information collection

As explained below, information collection is broadly classified under the following categories

  * When you complete a registration form.
  * When you use or interact with Adoptim services.
  * When you install or use the Adoptim plugin.
  * When you visit a website that directly or indirectly uses Adoptim services.
  * When you view or respond to advertisements served by us or on our behalf.

### Direct Information

Direct Information provide us with, case-n-point, on registration with us, you will be directly sharing information like such as name, email address, and other registration information. As required, you might be entitled to provide additional information about self in situations such as providing us phone number reach seek customer support.

### Usage Information

Usage information could refer to general click stream behavior, web pages viewed (including the URL addresses and content of such pages), search queries from which you are directed to a page, navigation from page to page through our publisher networks, time spent on each page, items that you click or select, IP address, cookie-based information, information about geographic location (e.g., derived from IP address), and Internet Service Provider.

### Cookie Information

Adoptim Site may use cookies or/and web beacons and information collected in our log files (such as Internet Protocol Address, referring URLs, etc.) about activity at this site to better our understanding in order to resolve technical issues thereby allowing a richer experience. Information from website analysis cookies or about website usage is not combined with information from any other Adoptim cookie. A third-party email program could be used to reach out to you via emails. We may use a third-party email technology to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Web beacons are used in those email messages to measure the effectiveness of our advertising.

### Technical Information

Technical information could refer to browser preference (e.g., Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox), OS, computer processing capacity and internet connecting preferences like USB, broadband etc.

### Information from Third Parties

We are likely to receive non-personal information (e.g., demographic information such as zip code) from our publishers, advertiser, and other third parties. For example, we are likely to receive publicly available information from third party websites with whom you have registered.

### C/ Information used by Adoptim

Usage of information can classified under the following broad need based situations  
Fulfill requests for our services.

In order to connect with you regarding sharing infor or responding to requests.  
Towards performing study on Adoptim service lines.

To enable you to create anan account and get registered.  
To reach out to you regarding Adoptim latest offering.  
Provide latest offerings for products and services of [Posu.me](http://posu.me/), Inc. and our partners, publishers, advertiser and other third parties. We may look to use Direct Information, Usage Information and/or Technical Information (alone or in combination) to assemble non-personal, demographic and behavioral information to group users that share a common interest into “Audience Segments.” These Audience Segments are not information that reveal user identity but defines user personality; for example, these segments may reveal a user’s geo or his interest in cars, but these segments would not reveal the name, e-mail address, phone number, mailing address, or user name of any specific individual.

This audience segments may be used for the following functions  
To create a match between advertising content and interested users  
To provide assistance and direction to publishers, advertiser and other third parties to create advertisements that maybe of high interest or use to the audience

In case, personally identifiable information (e.g., name) is publicly available through third party websites (e.g., social networks), we may seek consent to use that information in conjunction with services that we offer. However, we never disclose personal information without consent.

We and our publishers, advertiser and other third parties also use such information related purposes like research to improve our uderstanding of the behavioral aspect of users of the Adoptim services.

We may have a tie-up with a publisher that uses the services to collect Usage Information on such publisher’s websites, such as for the purpose of obtaining additional information about such publisher’s own users and in accordance with such publisher’s privacy policy (rather than for our independent purposes).We may use Technical Information to analyze browsing patterns and content, in order to personalize and target ads to you.

### D/ Sharing Information

Direct Information  
Our business is committed to neither sell nor share any direct information to third parties for any marketing related activities. The direct information stored with us herein is deemed secure.  
Personally identifiable information, maybe disclosed under the following situations  
On grounds of direct authorization by you (e.g. you directly respond to a third party offer on Adoptim services.  
If it is required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority.  
To protect our rights and property or the rights and property of the public or any user.

### E/ Information shared for advertising

The purpose of using non-personally identifiable Direct Information, Usage Information and/or Technical Information with third party advertisers and publishers is to assist them and us in providing advertising that is highly relevant and interesting to the discussed audience target segment. Our third party partners, advertisers and publishers may use a combination of information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) in order to provide advertisements that have the highest probability of being interesting to the end user.

Our publishers’ websites and their independent advertisers may independently collect other demographical information about you after they place their own cookies or web beacons on publishers’ websites. The use of cookies and pixel tags by our publishers, advertiser and other third parties are subject to their own privacy policies. We are not responsible for the information practices of these third parties.

### F/ Public information

When you post something in our website that has public access, for e.g. blogs response, please allow discretion towards deciding the nature of information that you are sharing

### G/ Authority

By accessing or using Adoptim services, you are ensuring that you are at least eighteen years of age, and that you have the right, authority and capacity to enter into legally binding agreements under applicable law of your country.

### H/ Acquisitions

In the event of a merger or acquisition with or by a different company, we would reserve the right to transfer information. In the event the that newly formed entity deiced to change its privacy policy, the same will be published on our website.

### I/ Security

We have undertaken very strict measures in an effort to help protect confidentiality of personally identifiable information however we cannot guarantee the confidentiality of the discussed as no technological environment is completely secure.

### J/ Changes in Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy by posting a notice of such change on our website. You should visit our website periodically to review any such change. When you continue to use or interact with [Posu.me](http://posu.me/) services after such change, subsequent provision of information (e.g., personally identifiable information) to us will be subject to such change. If such change materially expands our rights to use personally identifiable information that we have collected, we will notify you through email or a prominent posting on our website.

The Privacy Policy might undergo change with time and a subsequent notice of the same will reflect on our website. On continuing to interact with Adoptim services or website, our treatment of information may also be subjected to changes as per the policy.

### K/ Account Cancellation

If you may want to cancel account with us, you may send a mail to [contact@Adoptim.com](mailto:contact@Adoptim.com)

### L/ Retention

Information may be retained with us (Direct Information, Usage Information and/or Technical Information) as permitted by applicable law, but we hold the right to erradicate any such information without any liability to you.

### M/ How to Contact Us

If you have any further doubts regarding the privacy policies or its implementation, or you want to update account information inaccurate, you may send an email to: [contact@Adoptim.com](mailto:contact@Adoptim.com)
